Shizuka-san.
I brought the client who needs
an investigation.
This is Aya Sukiya.
An invisible person?
You are too?
Looks like Tonome in drag.
You don't have to say every thought
that enters your head.
"Tonome-san in drag"?
I'm sorry. She's a bit tactless.
You're Tonome-san, then?
Yes.
I've never met an invisible
person in the city before!
I'm so relieved to have
a member of my species helping me!
I'm happy to do so.
Please let us help you.
What a coincidence!
Shizuka.
I was surprised too.
Feeling self-conscious?
I thought the Tonome Detective Agency
would be able to handle this case.
H-How could you say that? She's a client!
Still...
It really must be a good sign!
Seems like they're getting
along real well, huh?
That happens when you don't run
into your own kind very often.
It's also my first time doing a job
for a member of my species.
Well... Akira-san's voice does sound
a bit friendlier than usual.
Tonome-san, were you born
in the invisible person village?
No, I was raised outside of it.
So you are self-conscious.
It's cute!
So was I!
MEETING ROOM
You've been accused of theft?
Yes.
The money went missing
from a safe at work.
No one was visible
on the security cameras.
The vice president decided that
an invisible person must have done it.
What did the president say?
The president is in the hospital.
The vice president's
been standing in.
I didn't do it, of course!
But the vice president seems
convinced it was me...
Even though he has no proof?
Yes.
And it's difficult to get an alibi,
since invisible people can't
be identified by their faces.
Sukiya-san was elsewhere that day,
but she doesn't know how to prove
it was her to establish an alibi.
Don't worry.
I promise I'll help you.
MEETING ROOM
Please do. Thank you.
I'm Gamaike. I'm standing
in for the president.
So she's hired a lawyer
and a private investigator, has she?
And you're an invisible person, too.
Do you think I could see the video
data from the security cameras?
Well... Of course you may.
I see.
It seems nobody interacted
with the safe between
when you last closed it and
when you opened it yesterday.
Yes, and that's why!
You invisible people have
that "full invisibility" thing
where you make your
clothes vanish too, right?
I'm thinking she must have used that!
E-Eh?
Where did the detective go?!
Excuse me.
That's how full invisibility works.
But it only makes us
invisible, not intangible.
Therefore...
There's no way she could steal money
from a safe that wasn't open.
W-Well then...
I suppose I got the wrong idea!
I'm sorry. The money went missing,
so I was just so shaken...
We actually have another
video to show you.
Starting a few days after you took
over for the president,
you were seen secretly depositing bills
into an ATM every day.
Fearing that you would be found out,
you decided to exploit
Sukiya-san's attributes
to lay the suspicion on her.
Isn't that right?
I believe that would
qualify as defamation.
Embezzlement, too.
What's going on here?!
M-Mr. President!
What were you doing while
I was hospitalized for appendicitis?!
I-It was a spur-of-the-moment thing...
This was clearly premeditated!
Thank you! You saved me!
The president explained
everything to the others,
so I'll be able to keep my job.
I'm glad your name was cleared.
I really can't thank you enough.
Everyone, thank you for running
such a swift investigation.
We were able to solve the case before
claims against our client went too far.
And while you have so many
other duties to see to...
We're fine. Shizuka made sure
all our schedules lined up.
We split it all up between
the three of us.
It was Yako's idea in the first place.
Shizuka-san's idea?
She wanted to do something to help you.
I-I really didn't do anything serious!
I was mostly supporting the other two!
And I'm sorry!
I shouldn't have gone so far!
I mean, but... why?
Because...
Even though he has no proof?
I could sense a little
anger in Akira-san's voice...
But I'm sure I can't tell him that.
Thank you, Shizuka-san.
You allowed us to save our client.
Oh, I know.
How about a little
company trip as thanks?
Hey, sounds great!
I wanna go to the mountains!
Great idea! How about camping?
You're coming too?
You don't even work here!
A mountain with a campground, then?
That was fast.
I can't wait for the tents and campfires!
Daichi, we can drive them!
It should be fun, right, Shizuka-san?
That's fine, but what about your job?
Akira-san's back to normal.
I'll take some paid days off, of course!
Yes, it should be fun!
You're really into this, huh?
It's mountain time!
River time!
Camping time!
Yeah!
Can you two help?
What's that asshole lawyer up to?
Setting up the smoker!
Why are you wearing
sunglasses, Shizuka-san?
You look very cool, though.
With all the trees around, there's a
good chance of taking a branch to the eye.
This is how I prevent that.
I see!
So, how can I help?
Would you mind grinding the beans
for when we take a break?
Okay!
Hey, I don't know how to put up a tent.
How about chopping wood, then?
You don't even need an ax!
You seem to like camping, Madaraito-san.
You got together most
of the camping equipment, too.
I actually used to hate the mountains.
But, thanks to Daichi,
I've come to love them.
Shizuka-san.
Would you like to take a walk with me?
Aren't all the sounds soothing?
The smells on the wind, too...
Would you prefer to slow down a bit?
No, this pace is perfect.
There's no fence for a while.
Would you prefer to walk
on the far side of the road?
What's on the other side of the fence?
A sharp incline, like a cliff.
We wouldn't want to fall off that!
But I feel safe knowing
you're here, Akira-san.
I feel safe knowing you're
here too, Shizuka-san.
That's right...
Akira-san had that scary experience
in the mountains that one time.
Are you really okay
with a trip to the mountains?
I did have some
lingering trauma about it,
but I feel like I can handle
anything if you're here,
so I completely forgot about the trauma!
I-I'm sure I'm not...
Hey, there's a bench.
Let's have a sit.
Um... I'm sure I'm not worth
that much to you.
But you already helped with
that invisible person case, didn't you?
That was nothing, really!
It's just...
Just what?
You don't usually get angry like that...
I'm sorry. Did I frighten you?
That's not what I mean!
I was just thinking, if you were
the one accused like that...
I start imagining it...
and it feels so sad and suffocating...
But then I think that maybe I should
have just minded my own business...
You don't have to worry about it so much.
Akira-san's sensations... His body heat,
his smell... It's suddenly so intense!
Historically, invisible people
have been treated with suspicion.
So I'm really glad that,
thanks to you and the others,
we were able to clear
the client's name completely.
But more important than that...
A-Akira-san?!
He's pressed against
my back... He's so warm!
You don't like this?
Nah... S'okay...
Did you just laugh? I felt
the slight shaking in your body!
I can't hide my feelings
from you, Shizuka-san.
That's what makes me the happiest.
I want you to uncover
more things about me.
W-Was that just...
I kissed you.
Should I not have?
No, it was okay, really!
Is it time to get back?
H-Hey...
Could we stay like this a bit longer?
Shall I do it again?
Well... I would find that...
unobjectionable.
Hey, they've been gone a while.
Here, all peeled.
You gotta have curry when you're camping!
Takes you back, huh?
You know, I used to hate the mountains.
I hated them so much,
I started to hold a grudge.
I'd think, "I'm gonna find the guy who
came up with school trips to the mountains
and sue him for all he's worth."
Madaraito, you okay?
You guys go on without me.
Yeah?
You sure?
Yeah, go on.
I'll catch up in my own time.
Well... catch you later, then.
Man, everyone's leaving me behind.
I hate school trips!
Hey, is that...
Kikira-kun?
We're in the same class,
but we've never talked before.
Still, what a relief.
It feels nice to know
that someone else is back here.
Having Kikira-kun here
has helped me keep going...
But...
I can't take anymore.
Kikira-kun?!
Thanks?
Huh?
H-Hey, wait! I can't make you do that!
Then walk faster already. Sheesh.
That sudden spike of tsun!
SUMMIT
It took you two a while.
Everyone else has already had lunch.
Kikira-kun.
Thanks for before.
Want to eat lunch with me?
Why?
Why?!
It's not like we're friends.
But... you helped me even
though we aren't friends!
It's like how you give up a seat
to a random old person on the train.
I'm like a random old person?!
Yeah.
Come on! It feels awkward
for me to eat by myself!
Eat with me!
Fine, if you want.
I'm so glad!
I get it. Kikira-kun's an awkward guy.
That's why I don't hear about him getting
dates, even though he's so good-looking.
You can have some of mine!
The fried chicken, then.
No shame at all!
Hey, let's sit together on the bus.
If you want.
I fell asleep.
Huh? Kikira-kun's asleep too.
And while he was sleeping...
It's gonna be awkward when he wakes up...
I'll try not to wake him...
Maybe just for a while...
Gotta sleep...
Wait, you weren't sleeping?!
So I can stay like this?!
Huh?
Huh?!
And that was that!
We just kind of started dating!
Man, he's always been
exhausting like that, huh?
So you held hands the whole way!
That's so beautiful!
There we go.
The river's slow here,
so it should be a good spot.
I hear the fishing's good here, too!
Your build makes
anything look flashy, huh?
And your stomach makes
anything look imposing, huh?
I'll lay out the tarp over here.
Huh? Where are those other two?
They said they'd catch up.
J-Jarashi-san!
Shizuka-san? Is something the matter?
Akira-san?!
Jarashi-san's already gone.
Should I call her?
N-No...
I guess maybe you could do it...
Could you come inside for a minute?
Excuse me.
I've never worn this swimsuit before.
I think I messed it up.
Huh? Akira-san?
Oh, well... I mean...
It looks like the other strap
is tangled in the frill.
Oh, I thought that might be it.
Did you choose this swimsuit?
No, Jarashi-san picked it for me.
I see.
It's really charming. I love it.
Really?! I'm so glad!
The cute!
Oh, right.
This came with it as well.
Should I put it on?
Let's do that.
We're here!
Shizuka, you're adorable!
Look at all of them!
Doesn't this feel nice?
Yes.
Hey, the fish are heading your way.
I got it.
Take that!
Jarashi-san, you're amazing.
That scared me!
Come try it, Tonome!
Me?
I'm afraid I'm hopeless.
Yeah, I bet.
Wait! Tonome, are you kinda jacked?
When your shirt gets wet,
it sticks to you,
and I can see your body's contours.
Oh, I see.
Akira-san is... well-muscled?
A-Akira-san! Shouldn't
you take your shirt off?
It's no fun to stand
around in wet clothes!
Yeah, that's true.
I can't really do that.
Why not?
Well, it's... how to put it...
If I take off my shirt, you'll be able to
see inside my bottoms from above...
And it's just... a little embarrassing.
I don't really get it.
I'm not sure I get it either.
We can't see it anyway.
It's just very embarrassing
for invisible people!
Hey, Jarashi.
Catch some more fish.
We'll cook 'em for lunch.
Hey, great idea!
Akira-san.
Could I say something?
What is it?
I don't like when other people...
uncover things about you.
Something like that.
I'm very sorry about that.
Sorry to interrupt the fun,
but could you do that somewhere else?
You can sleep if you want.
Nah, I'm okay.
Just let me know when you want
me to tag in at the wheel.
Like I'm gonna trust a guy who's yawning.
That's mean.
There's that inscrutable
kindness of yours.
Good thing I love it.
What in the world...
The others are fast asleep.
Coming home from a trip
always tires you out, huh?
I'm actually still awake...
I'd love to go on a trip just with her...
But it's probably too soon for that.
EPISODE 4: DON'T LET THEM EXPOSE YOU
TO BE CONTINUED